designbombs.com 2019-02-03

# Privacy Policy - Design Bombs

We value the privacy of our visitors here at Designbombs.com. In our privacy policy, we will detail what type of data we collect and store at Designbombs.com, as well as how we use it.

### Email Newsletter

We operate an email newsletter that you can voluntarily sign up for by entering your email and clicking **Subscribe**. In order to deliver this newsletter, we store your email address in MailChimp, our email marketing service.

We do not share your email address with any other third parties and you can unsubscribe at any time.

### Comments

If you voluntarily leave a comment at www.designbombs.com, we store the information entered into the form, as well as a visitor’s IP address and browser user-agent. The latter two pieces of data help us combat comment spam.

If you use the Gravatar service, an anonymized hash of your email address may be provided to Gravatar in order to check whether or not you’re using the service.

### Cookies & Data

A cookie is data that is stored on your hard drive to help us identify you and offer a better user experience.

We don’t collect any personal information unless it is absolutely needed, and we don’t share any of your data with third parties unless we’re legally compelled to.

This is a list of data that we potentially collect:

  *  **Google Analytics** – _ga, _gid, and _gat_gtag cookie data.
  *  **MailChimp** – we use mailchimp to store email addresses, you unsubscribe anytime.

### Your Rights To Data

If you have registered an account at www.designbombs.com or left a comment, you can request an exported file of all your stored personal data. You can also ask us to erase any personal data we have stored, but this does not include data we are obligated to keep for legal reasons.

### Protection Of Data

We take all reasonable measures possible to protect against unauthorized access of personally-identifying information.

### Changes To Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. As such, we encourage visitors to regularly check this page for Privacy Policy updates. Continuing to use www.designbombs.com after any change in this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of all changes.

To learn more or ask questions, you can use [our contact page](https://www.designbombs.com/contact/).
